Yes.
It is not from a regular job
And cannot be supplemented with the regular job.
We have a deep dive into the subject and you get the urge to try on one than the other.
I have friends who have participated in studies
For medicines and diet.
We found one where you can test sprouts for seven days.
It seems a little exciting.
Test sprouts for a week and get 1000 bucks.
You get to look out.
We have received some input on social media.
A tip about
that one could rebuild a garage or a room and rent out-
And get some extra slants.
We will talk about rental income later.
But it was a great tip.
Please continue to come up with tips and input.
Write to EFN's Instagram, Youtube comments field or live on Facebook.
You choose for yourself.
You can see the address at the bottom of the screen.
Keep in touch.
Continue to come up with questions, input and concerns.
Initially we can say that generally if one counts together
If there are over 20,000, it must be declared.
We want to point that.
Even if you have calculated that it should be tax -free ...
... maybe you have to declare it anyway.
-Remember that.
An alternative income that both you and I and many are already looking at
To invest in shares and funds so that you get a return.
You are a very good supporter.
You have a football team that you cheer for.
You might be able to rent out football supporters.
You set up and cheer for other teams.
You do not sell your soul.
We have with us a guest Marcus Lindblad-
And is good at.
That is what suits one.
How do you find out what you are good at does everyone have that self -insight?
That is a good question.
It is such a question that has taken me where I am today.
You have wanted to hunt around a bit and test a little different things.
Everything from ordering cans to selling things in flea or markets.
It got me into investment.
If you top the best.
That's what you are best at.
It is a good starting point.
Are there any that are at the bottom of the list
Worst, you say?
-Yes.
It is about how to value your time.
Do you have source criticism and analyzed the content
Thank you so much, Marcus.
Good tips you shared.
Thanks for being able to join.
-Bye!
Start with what you are good at.
It is a good theme for all alternative incomes.
What can I make money on the basis of my talents
What are people interested in this is about access and demand.
If you are good at something that everyone is good at, it is more difficult to pay.
If you are half good on something that stands out, you can be a little creative about it.
That you create that space and dare to take out the turns.
It is also about finding opportunities with what you have.
We have a deep dive in what applies.
I have basic dive anyway.
It can be good to carry with you.
It's pretty pretty
Very favorable tax rules for renting out a room, home or house.
You can rent for up to SEK 40,000 tax -free.
You may also make a deduction of 20 % of the rental income.
In practice, you can rent out for 50,000 a year tax -free.
It is still quite a lot.
This applies if you have a smaller house on the site
Or if you have an apartment.
When it comes to renting out a condominium ...
For houses it is different.
You own it and do not need to apply to rent.
But when it comes to an apartment, I have asked the rental committee about this.
You can rent out for up to three years without the rental committee saying no
to a tenant -owner association.
There may be reason why they say no.
But in general, they don't usually do it.
It usually lasts for one year at a time.
But it is always good to check with its tenant association.
That is what is good to know about renting out your home.
These are quite clear and nice conditions in any case up to 50,000.
After 50,000, there is 30 % tax on rental income.
What can one more do to make money
We talked a little about surveys.
It's new for this season, and it's fun.
One can also, as many of you who follow us, invest
And take part in value growth in that way.
We will not dive into it, but ...
Dividends are below that category.
We have made sections on how to think when investing in shares and funds.
In Youtube flow I see that Elin has written:
"Maybe a credit card with cashback can be counted as alternative income"
Yes, I think so.
-Yes actually.
I saw a documentary about a person living on it.
Does he live on it?
-Yes.
Don't ask me how it goes together.
I didn't look so carefully at that section.
But it was a documentary on the theme of personal finance.
Fun.
Loppis, then can you make money from it?
Yes, you can earn up to 50,000 on flea ice cream.
Without tax?
-No, it must be declared.
It is definitely an extra income.
How much do you need to sell for 50,000?
-Is the 50,000 limit?
Under 50,000 there is no tax.
But you have to declare
If it is over 50,000, it is counted as income from business activities.
You can also pick berries, mushrooms and cones.
It's a little special.
I wonder why it has been picked out.
You thought it was a tradition here.
-Yes, it was a guess.
You can pick cones.
You can sell them in the inner city at Christmas.
In Stockholm, Gothenburg or where you live.
There you get better paid than if you are in someone's forest.
It's like selling sand in the desert.
You can earn SEK 12,500, tax -free.
That's a tip.
But it takes time to pick.
I would focus on cloudberries.
It is the best margin on it
Yes, cloudberries and blueberries, I tip.
It's probably pretty good.
The deer is probably the most expensive.
I think we ... I've started here.
I thought we would rate
Based on our spontaneous feeling, slightly different types of alternative income.
It is about how exciting they feel and how lucrative we feel they are.
It will be a summary rating.
We'll have a look at this.
You can start and take the press.
To respond to surveys, the first?
-Yes, on scale 1-5.
That's why I got nothing.
It was so simple.
"Multilevel Marketing" is in some cases ...
It is in a gray zone and can in some cases be considered pyramid scheme.
It's a little sensitive.
I am very little familiar with this, but it will be a money bag.
I am afraid that people will be exploited and do not like that feeling.
I also put a 1st on it, for ... -or 2.
I sneak in a 2nd.
No.
On the one hand, you often need to buy different starting packages.
Then you have to invest money.
Then it is difficult to discern which ones are serious.
Some are of the more serious kind and some are of the rogue kind.
It is not always easy to discern.
You can do surveys, google and take references and so on.
References are difficult, because there is probably someone who makes money.
When recruiting, they make money.
They have incentives to say it's good.
Good.
Rent out gadgets.
-It's great if you have the opportunity.
One might be renting out a boat or a caravan
And if it gets scalable, then you can make a lot of money.
You can spend some time on static content, different types of leaderboards or guides
Which does not need to be updated so often.
However, there is fierce competition.
Because there is a lot of money to be made if you are good
Has it attracted many talented.
Selling cones, then?
-It's fun and nice.
It is quick to fill a bucket.
Sell it expensive in Stockholm's inner city.
Forward Christmas.
Post a shock.
We say 3.
It is designed to get back pain.
I set a 1st p.g.a.
My sore back.
After the race this weekend.
-Exactly.
It was already bad.
Good.
Then we have rated different types of alternative income.
Question: "Do you rent things out through an app service or entirely yourself"
I have not tried to rent things out, but I would have liked to use a service.
On the one hand, the payment is right.
On the one hand, they help with different types of insurance.
You can easily reach the right target group.
If you are going to rent out your apartment
There are platforms for people looking for apartment.
It is also an advantage.
One thing we should lift is to write a book.
If you initially spend some time writing and creating content
Can you make money for a long time and build a brand around the subject.
Nice